<? xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<games>
  <gname>Prison Architects</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/233450/header.jpg?t=1444663527</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/256657032/movie480.webm?t=1444125098</gvid>
  <gprice>$35</gprice>
  <gdesc>Build and Manage A Maximum Security Prison.

Build and manage a Maximum Security Prison. As the sun casts it’s early morning rays on a beautiful patch of countryside the clock starts ticking. You’ve got to crack on and build a holding cell to detain the job­ lot of maximum security prisoners that are trundling to your future prison on their yellow bus. As your workmen lay the last brick you don’t have a moment to let them rest as they need to get started on the first proper cell block so you can make room for the next prisoner intake. Once they’ve all got a place to lay their weary heads the fun can really start.

You’ll need a canteen, infirmary and a guard room, oh, and don’t forget to plumb in a toilet, or things will get messy, but what about a workout area? Or solitary confinement cells? Or an execution chamber?

Inspired by Dungeon Keeper, Dwarf Fortress and Theme Hospital and with over 1 million players having spent time inside, Prison Architect is the world’s best lock-­em-­up.

Story Mode

Prison Architect opens with the story of Edward, a man facing the electric chair for committing a crime of passion. This is followed by four additional chapters focusing on different characters and aspects of prison life. From Mafia Dons to power-crazed senators, Prison Architect has them all! To bring these characters to life, Introversion teamed up with award winning professional writer Chris Hastings, producing an enthralling tale of corruption and human misery set against the background of the modern prison industrial complex.

Escape Mode

Finished your supermax? Got guard dogs roving every corridor and prisoners eating out of your hand? Now you can live the horror by firing up escape mode and play as a prisoner hell-bent on getting the hell out of dodge.

Dig a tunnel, go for the armoury or start a riot and slip out in the chaos, it’s entirely up to you! Figure out how to escape from your own creation, or hit the random button and load one of the 12,000 prisons created by the steam community, whichever you choose it’s not going to be easy.</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>GameDev Tycoon</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/239820/header.jpg?t=1416987202</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2029163/movie480.webm?t=1377104335</gvid>
  <gprice>$15</gprice>
  <gdesc>In Game Dev Tycoon you replay the history of the gaming industry by starting your own video game development company in the 80s. Create best selling games. Research new technologies and invent new game types. Become the leader of the market and gain worldwide fans.
A journey through gaming history
Start in the 80s
Start your adventure in a small garage office in the 80s. Enjoy the hand-crafted level design while you develop your first simple games. Gain experience, unlock new options and create your first game engine.

Create games your way
In Game Dev Tycoon the decisions you make during development really matter. Decide which areas you want to focus on. Does your game need more gameplay or should you focus more on quests? These decisions will have a major impact on the success of your game.

Grow your company
Once you have successfully released a few games you can move into your own office and forge a world-class development team. Hire staff, train them and unlock new options.

Make larger more complex games
With experience and a good team, you can release larger, more complex games. Larger games bring new challenges and you will have to manage your team well to deliver hit games.
Features
Start a game development company in the 80s
Design and create games
Gain new insights through game reports
Research new technologies
Create custom game engines
Move into bigger offices
Forge a world-class development team
Unlock secret labs
Conduct industry changing products
Unlock achievements
Modding support
Workshop support
Community translations for German, Spanish, French, Portoguese (Brazil), Russian, Czech, Swedish, Dutch and Italian are available through the in-game menu.

The full game has many more features which are not listed here to prevent spoilers.</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>Limbo</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/48000/header.jpg?t=1404392129</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/80896/movie480.webm?t=1311111542</gvid>
  <gprice>$15</gprice>
  <gdesc>Uncertain of his sister's fate, a boy enters LIMBO</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>Fallout 4</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/377160/header.jpg?t=1444335558</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/256656644/movie480.webm?t=1442933162</gvid>
  <gprice>$90</gprice>
  <gdesc>DESCRIPTION:

Bethesda Game Studios, the award-winning creators of Fallout 3 and The Elder Scrolls V: Skyrim, welcome you to the world of Fallout 4 – their most ambitious game ever, and the next generation of open-world gaming.

As the sole survivor of Vault 111, you enter a world destroyed by nuclear war. Every second is a fight for survival, and every choice is yours. Only you can rebuild and determine the fate of the Wasteland. Welcome home.


KEY FEATURES:
Freedom and Liberty!
Do whatever you want in a massive open world with hundreds of locations, characters, and quests. Join multiple factions vying for power or go it alone, the choices are all yours.

You’re S.P.E.C.I.A.L!
Be whoever you want with the S.P.E.C.I.A.L. character system. From a Power Armored soldier to the charismatic smooth talker, you can choose from hundreds of Perks and develop your own playstyle.

Super Deluxe Pixels!
An all-new next generation graphics and lighting engine brings to life the world of Fallout like never before. From the blasted forests of the Commonwealth to the ruins of Boston, every location is packed with dynamic detail.

Violence and V.A.T.S.!
Intense first or third person combat can also be slowed down with the new dynamic Vault-Tec Assisted Targeting System (V.A.T.S) that lets you choose your attacks and enjoy cinematic carnage.

Collect and Build!
Collect, upgrade, and build thousands of items in the most advanced crafting system ever. Weapons, armor, chemicals, and food are just the beginning - you can even build and manage entire settlements.</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>This War of Mine</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/282070/header.jpg?t=1444262667</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2035302/movie480.webm?t=1414688488</gvid>
  <gprice>$25</gprice>
  <gdesc>In This War Of Mine you do not play as an elite soldier, rather a group of civilians trying to survive in a besieged city; struggling with lack of food, medicine and constant danger from snipers and hostile scavengers. The game provides an experience of war seen from an entirely new angle.

The pace of This War of Mine is imposed by the day and night cycle. During the day snipers outside stop you from leaving your refuge, so you need to focus on maintaining your hideout: crafting, trading and taking care of your survivors. At night, take one of your civilians on a mission to scavenge through a set of unique locations for items that will help you stay alive.

Make life-and-death decisions driven by your conscience. Try to protect everybody from your shelter or sacrifice some of them for longer-term survival. During war, there are no good or bad decisions; there is only survival. The sooner you realize that, the better.
This War of Mine:
Inspired by real-life events
Control your survivors and manage your shelter
Craft weapons, alcohol, beds or stoves – anything that helps you survive
Make decisions - an often unforgiving and emotionally difficult experience
Randomized world and characters every time you start a new game
Charcoal-stylized aesthetics to complement the game's theme

Previews:
IGN
This War of Mine might be the war game we need.
Gamespot
I was intrigued by This War of Mine's attempts to portray the consequences of war in a way that games have largely ignored in the past. The fact that the psychological and emotional challenges of living under such horrifying conditions are something you have to consider as you struggle gives me added hope that it might treat its hefty and important subject matter with the gravity and complexity that it deserves.
Game Informer
11bit is blazing a new thematic trail amidst the currently popular survival genre, and so far the studio seems to have something special on its hand.</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>Saints Row IV</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/206420/header.jpg?t=1425491496</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2028935/movie480.webm?t=1377010759</gvid>
  <gprice>$25</gprice>
  <gdesc>The US President must save the Earth from alien overlord Zinyak using an arsenal of superpowers and strange weapons in the wildest open world game ever.

The epic conclusion to the game that changed all the rules! The Saints have gone from the crackhouse to the White House—but the Earth has been invaded and it’s up to you to free the world from Overlord Zinyak and his alien empire. With homies new and old by your side, and an arsenal of superpowers and strange weapons, you must save the world in the wildest open world game ever!
Key Features
The American (Fever) Dream – Play as the President of the United States in a story that spans countries, space, and time. Saints Row IV is to Saints Row: The Third what Saints Row: The Third is to Do The Right Thing. You’re not ready.
Super Hero-in-Chief – Leap over buildings. Kill people with your mind. Run through tanks. Those are some of the most mundane powers you will wield in your quest to stop an alien menace hell-bent on destroying the Earth.
Alien Toys of Destruction - Wield an impressive array of alien vehicles and weapons… FOR SCIENCE!
Custom Weapons, Custom Mayhem – You’ve customized your character. You’ve customized your clothes. Now you can complete the look with our all new weapon customization system. Turn traditional weapons into exotic conversation pieces!
Dynamic Duo - Seamless drop-in, drop-out co-op, a Saints Row standard, improved. The only thing better than one malicious super-powered President is two.</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/292030/header.jpg?t=1444689672</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2038478/movie480.webm?t=1436223406</gvid>
  <gprice>$50</gprice>
  <gdesc>The Witcher: Wild Hunt is a story-driven, next-generation open world role-playing game set in a visually stunning fantasy universe full of meaningful choices and impactful consequences. In The Witcher you play as the professional monster hunter, Geralt of Rivia, tasked with finding a child of prophecy in a vast open world rich with merchant cities, viking pirate islands, dangerous mountain passes, and forgotten caverns to explore.

PLAY AS A HIGHLY TRAINED MONSTER SLAYER FOR HIRE
Trained from early childhood and mutated to gain superhuman skills, strength and reflexes, witchers are a distrusted counterbalance to the monster-infested world in which they live.
Gruesomely destroy foes as a professional monster hunter armed with a range of upgradeable weapons, mutating potions and combat magic.
Hunt down a wide range of exotic monsters from savage beasts prowling the mountain passes to cunning supernatural predators lurking in the shadows of densely populated towns.
Invest your rewards to upgrade your weaponry and buy custom armour, or spend them away in horse races, card games, fist fighting, and other pleasures the night brings.

EXPLORE A MORALLY INDIFFERENT FANTASY OPEN WORLD
Built for endless adventure, the massive open world of The  Witcher sets new standards in terms of size, depth and complexity.
Traverse a fantastical open world: explore forgotten ruins, caves and shipwrecks, trade with merchants and dwarven smiths in cities, and hunt across the open plains, mountains and seas.
Deal with treasonous generals, devious witches and corrupt royalty to provide dark and dangerous services.
Make choices that go beyond good & evil, and face their far-reaching consequences.

CHASE DOWN THE CHILD OF PROPHECY
Take on the most important contract to track down the child of prophecy, a key to save or destroy this world.
In times of war, chase down the child of prophecy, a living weapon of power, foretold by ancient elven legends.
Struggle against ferocious rulers, spirits of the wilds and even a threat from beyond the veil – all hell-bent on controlling this world.
Define your destiny in a world that may not be worth saving.

FULLY REALIZED NEXT GENERATION
Built exclusively for next generation hardware, the REDengine 3 renders the world of The Witcher visually nuanced and organic, a real true to life fantasy.
Dynamic weather systems and day/night cycles affect how the citizens of the towns and the monsters of the wilds behave.
Rich with storyline choices in both main and subplots, this grand open world is influenced by the player unlike ever before.</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>Counter Strike: Global Offensive (CS: GO)</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/730/header.jpg?t=1444165321</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/81954/movie480.webm?t=1432922939</gvid>
  <gprice>$10</gprice>
  <gdesc>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive (CS: GO) will expand upon the team-based action gameplay that it pioneered when it was launched 14 years ago.

CS: GO features new maps, characters, and weapons and delivers updated versions of the classic CS content (de_dust, etc.). In addition, CS: GO will introduce new gameplay modes, matchmaking, leader boards, and more.

"Counter-Strike took the gaming industry by surprise when the unlikely MOD became the most played online PC action game in the world almost immediately after its release in August 1999," said Doug Lombardi at Valve. "For the past 12 years, it has continued to be one of the most-played games in the world, headline competitive gaming tournaments and selling over 25 million units worldwide across the franchise. CS: GO promises to expand on CS' award-winning gameplay and deliver it to gamers on the PC as well as the next gen consoles and the Mac."</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>Goat Simulator</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/265930/header.jpg?t=1435055492</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2035686/movie480.webm?t=1416516482</gvid>
  <gprice>$5</gprice>
  <gdesc>Goat Simulator is the latest in goat simulation technology, bringing next-gen goat simulation to YOU. You no longer have to fantasize about being a goat, your dreams have finally come true! WASD to write history.

Gameplay-wise, Goat Simulator is all about causing as much destruction as you possibly can as a goat. It has been compared to an old-school skating game, except instead of being a skater, you're a goat, and instead of doing tricks, you wreck stuff. Destroy things with style, such as doing a backflip while headbutting a bucket through a window, and you'll earn even more points! Or you could just give Steam Workshop a spin and create your own goats, levels, missions, and more! When it comes to goats, not even the sky is the limit, as you can probably just bug through it and crash the game.
Disclaimer
Goat Simulator is a completely stupid game and, to be honest, you should probably spend your money on something else, such as a hula hoop, a pile of bricks, or maybe pool your money together with your friends and buy a real goat.
Key Features
You can be a goat
Get points for wrecking stuff - brag to your friends that you're the alpha goat
Steam Workshop support - make your own goats, levels, missions, game modes, and more!
MILLIONS OF BUGS! We're only eliminating the crash-bugs, everything else is hilarious and we're keeping it
In-game physics that bug out all the time
Seriously look at that goat's neck
You can be a goat
Mac and Linux Disclaimer
The Mac and Linux ports are still in Beta. Expect problems. We're working on fixing them asap!</gdesc>
</games>

<games>
  <gname>Sid Meier's Civilization® V</gname>
  <gimg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/8930/header.jpg?t=1436891075</gimg>
  <gvid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/5690/movie480.webm?t=1413827694</gvid>
  <gprice>$60</gprice>
  <gdesc>The Flagship Turn-Based Strategy Game Returns

Become Ruler of the World by establishing and leading a civilization from the dawn of man into the space age: Wage war, conduct diplomacy, discover new technologies, go head-to-head with some of history’s greatest leaders and build the most powerful empire the world has ever known.

INVITING PRESENTATION: Jump right in and play at your own pace with an intuitive interface that eases new players into the game. Civ veterans will appreciate the depth, detail and control that are highlights of the series.
BELIEVABLE WORLD: Ultra realistic graphics showcase lush landscapes for you to explore, battle over and claim as your own. Art deco influences abound in the menus and icons in the most well-designed Civ ever developed.
COMMUNITY & MULTIPLAYER: Compete with Civ players all over the world or locally in LAN matches, mod* the game in unprecedented ways, and install mods directly from an in-game community hub without ever leaving the game. Civilization V brings community to the forefront.
WIDE SYSTEM COMPATIBILITY: Civilization V operates on many different systems, from high end DX11 desktops to many laptops. Enjoy unlimited installations on multiple PCs with your Steam account and take your Civ V experience with you everywhere you go.
ALL NEW FEATURES: A new hex-based gameplay grid opens up exciting new combat and build strategies. City States become a new resource in your diplomatic battleground. An improved diplomacy system allows you to negotiate with fully interactive leaders. Custom music scores and orchestral recordings give Civ V the level of polish and quality you expect from the series.
SOCIALLY RESPONSIBLE: 2K Games is donating a total of $250,000 to four education based charities, and users' choices will determine how the money is dispersed: simply select your choice from the pre-selected charities during the install process.†
*Modding SDK available post launch as a free download.

† Charity selection available until Dec. 31, 2010. Not valid in all territories.

Note: The Mac and Linux + SteamOS versions of Sid Meier's Civilization V are available in English, French, Italian, German and Spanish only.</gdesc>
</games>

<software>
  <sname>Music Creator 7</sname>
  <simg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/346590/header.jpg?t=1439936841</simg>
  <svid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2037502/movie480.webm?t=1426790618</svid>
  <sprice>$50</sprice>
  <sdesc>Introducing Music Creator 7
No musical experience? No worries. Music Creator 7 is the fun, easy, and fast way to create original music or remix your favorite songs. Transform any Windows 7 or 8 computer into your own personal music studio with all the tools, loops, instruments, and effects you need to create, edit, and mix great music.

Version 7 of this best-selling software makes it even easier to produce exceptional tracks thanks to the integrated MixStrip, one-knob “Style Dial FX” for shaping your sound, touch screen compatibility, and VST3 plug-in standard support—so you can use cutting-edge instruments and effects from Cakewalk and dozens of other manufacturers.

Then when you’re ready to share your music with the world post your music on Facebook and Twitter with SoundCloud.
Experience the joy of creating music today—Music Creator 7 makes it easy.

Highlights:
Seamlessly create, record, edit, and mix your music using the award-winning Skylight user interface
NEW! Access all your most important controls using the Hi-Def Control Bar with more harmonious spacing, labeling, and dynamic resizing
NEW! Create your own MIDI parts with the new virtual onscreen MIDI controller with touch support, or your QWERTY keyboard—great for mobile music making
Get creative with 32 audio tracks and 8 instrument tracks, and 128 MIDI tracks
NEW! Support for 8 inputs and 8 outputs simultaneously
NEW! Support for the latest VST3 instruments and effects
A complete backing band with 6 virtual instruments (including the entire Studio Instruments Suite)
NEW! Mix like a pro with the integrated MixStrip, which includes Curve EQ and new Style Dial FX for one knob access to commonly used effects
Mix with all the must-have effects including reverb, EQ, and more
Plug in your guitar and rock out with Overloud’s TH2 Creator guitar amp simulator
NEW! Enhanced MIDI editing includes a new Piano Roll View and time-saving Pattern tool for painting MIDI parts
NEW! Create the perfect performance from multiple takes using the new comp tool
Create beats and drum tracks with the integrated Step Sequencer
Trigger audio and MIDI loops for real-time performance and remixing with the Matrix View
Custom modern loops designed by Loopmasters
Easily drag and drop loops, instruments, effects, and track templates from the built-in Browser
Plus! Use any Windows 8 touch-enabled device to control the software with your fingers

What's New in Music Creator 7
Music Creator 7 now includes many exciting, easy-to-understand new features that allow even beginners to obtain professional-sounding results.

Hi-Def Control Bar
Regardless of screen size, the new Hi-Def Control Bar makes it even easier to access your most frequently used controls. With clearer text, and better auto spacing, the new Control Bar makes creating music an absolute joy on the eyes. And with dynamic resizing, your Control Bar will always look good regardless of your PC screen’s resolution.

Onscreen Virtual Controller
Programming MIDI synth lines and beats has never been more fun, thanks to the new onscreen virtual MIDI controller—play your parts right from your touch screen with any multi-touch compatible monitor or PC. You can also use any QWERTY keyboard, so you don’t need to carry around a separate hardware MIDI controller.

MixStrip
The new MixStrip, integrated directly into Music Creator’s Track View, makes it easy to achieve superior mixes in less time. The MixStrip includes the built-in, high-quality Curve EQ on every track, and the new Style Dial FX offer speedy, one-knob access to the most commonly used effects including:

GRIT: Tube warmth mixed in with modern amp overdrive
MAX: Transparent track leveler and compressor for everyday use
SPACE: Dynamically shaped ambience control for small to huge sounds.

Improved Audio Editing
Music Creator 7 now features Cakewalk’s unique “speed comping,” so you can assemble a perfect performance from multiple takes with a simple swipe of the mouse – ideal for vocals and guitar solos. And you’ll be clicking less than ever thanks to the Smart Tool, which adapts to your workflow - whether you’re editing audio or MIDI data. Also, editing is a snap with the Smart Grid—which automatically sets the snap resolution and visual grid line to match the current zoom level.

Enhanced editing
The only variable separating you from your creativity is time, and the Pattern Tool—which sits in the Smart Tool palette for instant access—is all about saving time. Forget cut and paste: Simply select and paint MIDI loops and patterns across the Piano Roll View and Track View. In addition, Music Creator now allows for MIDI time-stretching, velocity layering, and additional functionality to simplify MIDI editing even further. And it’s all wrapped in a brand new Piano Roll View with improved zoom that makes editing MIDI a piece of cake.

Expand your Creative Palette with Cakewalk add-ons</sdesc>
</sotftware>

<software>
  <sname>MAGIX Music Maker 2015 Premium</sname>
  <simg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/319980/header.jpg?t=1431426201</simg>
  <svid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2034158/movie480.webm?t=1410176164</svid>
  <sprice>$55</sprice>
  <sdesc>Drag & drop to create your own songs with MAGIX Music Maker 2015. You have complete control of all instruments and tools right from the start - no previous experience is required. Your equipment includes more than 3000 sounds & loops, two powerful synthesizers and a heavy-hitting drum machine with an 8-bit look.

MAGIX Music Maker lets you be a musician, singer or a producer. Immerse yourself in a world of hip hop, reggae, techno or rock and create your own song. Every sound has a different story - and you get to decide how that story is told.
Your basic equipment:
Drag, drop and arrange more than 3000 loops & sounds
Six different Soundpools from diverse genres
Urban Drums: A drum machine for Hip Hop & Dubstep
Analog Synths: A virtual synthesizer for an electronic sound
DN-e1 synthesizer for a high-quality synthetic sound
Up to 99 tracks for your own songs
Vocal Tune 2: Tuning for vocal recordings
Screen keyboard: Make music with your mouse
Professional studio effects & plug-ins
VST 2 support
Import projects from the free Music Maker Jam app
A ton of fun


Amazing effects You can individually adjust the loudness of each of 99 tracks and apply effects to any of them with the click of a mouse. From vintage to high-end effects: Take your sound to the next level.
New instruments
All the instruments in Music Maker 2015 can be played with the mouse, the screen keyboard or a USB keyboard.

Drum pads instead of game pads
Turn on the new Urban Drums virtual drum machine and find something to hold on to: These powerful drums are perfect for making Hip Hop and Dubstep beats.

The ultimate synthesizer
Unbeatable: The Analog Synths virtual instrument brings the sounds of legendary analog synthesizers back from the grave and unites them in one powerful package.

Individualize your sound
Become the hero of an entire generation: The Vita Sampler allows you to use sound files from games and other pieces of music to create your own instrument. Endlessly modifiable.</sdesc>
</sotftware>

<software>
  <sname>Virtual DJ - Broadcaster Edition</sname>
  <simg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/224380/header.jpg?t=1380021165</simg>
  <svid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3J1XvjB11r8</svid>
  <sprice>$60</sprice>
  <sdesc>VirtualDJ is revolutionary software which allows audio and video mixing right from a computer. VirtualDJ is simple and intuitive to use but do not be fooled — there are many advanced features to explore and customize.

VirtualDJ features everything you need for imaginative performance and mixing:

Two virtual decks for loading audio and video tracks, short clips and karaoke
Extensive browsing functions utilizing ID3 tag and custom information fields
Comprehensive mixer with all the features that you would expect from a traditional mixer (EQ, gain, crossfader)
Audio and video effects processors
Linking video to audio tracks for pre-selected visual enhancement to the audio
Sampler for recording and playing back audio clips on the fly
ClipBank for playing back video clips on the fly
Smart and User-Defined (IN/OUT) Looping engine
Real-time recording of your mixes ( Audio and Video )
Real-time webcasting of your sessions
Additionally, VirtualDJ includes many innovative features to help you spend less time with the tedious, time-consuming aspects of DJing and mixing:

Analysis of Beats Per Minute (BPM) and Key detection for Harmonic Mixing
Automatic beat matching for quick mixing
Computer Beat Grid for easy visual mixing
Dynamic Hot Cue points
VirtualDJ is the most complete and extensive DJ software on the market today. It provides an exhaustive set of features for you to take advantage of and create great mixes. Whether you are a beginner or a professional DJ, you will find working inside VirtualDJ to be fun, intuitive and highly efficient.</sdesc>
</sotftware>

<software>
  <sname>GG Maker</sname>
  <simg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/347400/header.jpg?t=1438088105</simg>
  <svid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/2040754/movie480.webm?t=1436897333</svid>
  <sprice>$50</sprice>
  <sdesc>GG Maker is an easy but powerful tool for building games to share on PC and mobile devices. Boasting the engine’s own Graphically Assisted Scripting, GG Maker accommodates beginners and advanced developers alike. Build your dreams effortlessly, then share your creations across multiple platforms.

About This Software
Boasting powerful tools for beginners and advanced users alike, GG Maker is the new, cutting-edge engine for developing and sharing your own games. Even if you have never had prior experience with code and scripting, this engine will accommodate you and help your skills grow. Whatever vision you have for your game, GG Maker is there to do the hard work for you.

With GG Maker’s well thought-out features, making your own game has never been so accessible until now. Utilize exceptional tools to bring out your creativity:
Sophisticated map editor for areas with elevation and drama, making use of dynamic lights, fog, color tints and weather.
Flexible artificial intelligence which gives your characters depth and interactivity.
Unique characters with sprite customization, allowing you to change visible clothing and equipment in-game.
Innovative HUD and menu editor tools for custom interfaces and heads-up displays, loading screens, menus, dialogue boxes, health, equipment, or anything your game demands.

Share Your Games With Anyone, Anywhere
As GG Maker allows your creations to be ported to mobile devices such as Android and iOS (coming soon), it couldn’t be easier to show off your games on the go. Installation setup files for your projects are built within the engine, meaning sharing games is fuss-free and fast. You can even distribute your game for sale!

Graphically Assisted Scripting
Creating your own game can be done to your exact specification by using GG Maker’s ingenious graphical scripting. While much more advanced users are given the option to use raw code, beginners are offered the comfort of intuitive UIs which help to build the game around variables and branches using a hands-on interface. The engine also offers built-in scripts such as doors, chests, keys and locks, and templates for characters and enemies for an even more relaxed game design experience.

Make Your Vision A Reality
Designing and creating your own game has never been so easy with GG Maker’s innovative tools. Make any game you can think of, including RPGs, shoot-‘em-ups, racing games, fighting games, simulation games, platformers, tower defense, card games, and even 3D games! If you can imagine it, you can build it with GG Maker.</sdesc>
</software>

<software>
  <sname>Marmoset Toolbag 2</sname>
  <simg>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/362750/header.jpg?t=1439831920</simg>
  <svid>http://cdn.akamai.steamstatic.com/steam/apps/256655312/movie480.webm?t=1438977048</svid>
  <sprice>$100</sprice>
  <sdesc>Marmoset Toolbag™ is a full-featured, real-time material editor and renderer bundled in a tidy package. Toolbag provides a powerful and efficient workflow, bringing exemplary rendering quality to every stage of the 3D art pipeline. For R&D, from pre-production to post-production, Toolbag is an essential tool for every 3D artist. Use Toolbag as a final presentation tool for your artwork, a high fidelity viewer for asset sharing and internal reviews, or simply as a material and texture map previewer. Or just have fun with it - we think you'll like what you see.
Dota 2 Support!
With full shader support to match Dota 2's material setup, Toolbag 2 is a great visualization and final render tool for your Steam Workshop asset development. Directly import a Valve Material Type (.vmt) to get started quickly. Check out our Dota 2 Shader overview: http://vimeo.com/87235066.
Export to Web
Toolbag 2 includes our very own Marmoset Viewer, a WebGL viewer that delivers a 3D web experience second to none - no plugin required. Construct your scene in Toolbag and export a high quality 3D presentation with the click of a button. Viewer runs on thousands of devices and a variety of browsers, with support for Windows, OS X, iOS and Android operating systems. Check out the Viewer intro video: http://vimeo.com/120704661
Full Scene Ahead
Toolbag has been greatly expanded to include a full suite of scene editing tools. Control multiple meshes, lights, cameras, and groups with a completely rebuilt user interface. The new, centralized Toolbag scene file (.tbscene) makes for simple and straightforward transferability, and dynamic mesh and texture reloading ensure a lossless workflow.
Light Your Way
The new sky editor features instantaneous processing of background images and one-click light creation. Combined with directional, spot, and omni lights with gels and soft shadows, the new lighting system is ready to put your work in its best light.
Get Physical
Toolbag 2 also brings rendering features for physically-based shading workflows. With options for energy conservation, "metalness", realistic Fresnel, and self-occlusion, Toolbag is ready to meet the needs of modern art production. To have you up and running quickly, Toolbag 2 ships with a full set of physically-based preset materials, featuring PBR scan data.
Material Goods
Toolbag 2's modular material system makes a vast array of combinations possible. Choose the modules that work for you and your workflow from an expanded array of shaders. Alongside the basic albedo, specular, gloss, and normal settings, you will find:

Dynamic Tessellation
PN Triangle mesh smoothing
Height & Vector Displacement modes
Detail Normal Maps
Parallax Occlusion Maps
"Metalness" Maps
GGX, Blinn-Phong, & Anisotropic Reflections
Secondary Reflections
Skin Diffusion
Microfiber ("Fuzz") Diffusion
Occlusion and Cavity Maps
Emissive Maps
Dota 2 and Unreal 4 templates
Allegorithmic Substances support
Dithered Supersampled Transparency
...and more on the way!</sdesc>
</software>


<hardware>
  <hname>Playstation 4</hname>
  <himg>http://cdn2.expertreviews.co.uk/sites/expertreviews/files/styles/article_main_wide_image/public/images/dir_417/er_photo_208585.jpg?itok=IsgW_Osd</himg>
  <hvid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lt5BIWc8R8s</hvid>
  <hprice>$555</hprice>
  <hdesc>The surface of the new PS4 system’s HDD bay cover will come in a matte finish, giving the system a more casual look.  With the new system, users can continue to enjoy unique and interactive entertainment experiences only available on PlayStation®, including the wide array of game titles and strong network offerings.

Offering twice the storage of the existing PS4, you’ll be able to download more of the games you love to your PS4, extend your play with more great add-on content and save and share even more of your best gaming highlights.

Designed by the most inventive minds in video games, PlayStation 4 will let game creators unleash their imaginations to develop cutting-edge experiences never before possible.

Ultra-fast processors, advanced graphics performance and unrivalled system memory. What does that mean for the games you'll play? They're bigger, faster, more innovative. And more than you ever imagined.

Key Features

DualShock 4 - Complete Control
Interact with games in all the ways you're used to, and some you never expected. As well as more precise dual analog sticks and inbuilt motion sensors, DUALSHOCK®4 also includes touch controls and the innovative SHARE button.

Remote Play - PlayStation®4 Games in the Palm of Your Hand
Play your favourite PlayStation®4 games on your PlayStation®Vita system's beautiful 5-inch display using Remote Play.

SHARE button - Share the fun instantly
Use the SHARE button on DUALSHOCK®4 to share your gameplay videos and pictures in the blink of an eye. Stream your live gameplay to Ustream or record, edit and upload videos to Facebook in seconds.

PlayStation® App - Stay Connected with PlayStation
Chat with your friends, watch their latest gameplay videos and give them tips using the PlayStation® App for mobile and tablet devices.

Label - Sony Computer Entertainment Aus Pty Ltd

^Discounts apply to most rece</hdesc>
</hardware>

<hardware>
  <hname>Xbox One</hname>
  <himg>http://compass.xboxlive.com/assets/93/76/93764cb0-0ab4-4400-8539-fbd37958d1de.png?n=Meet1.png</himg>
  <hvid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0SSUCfg0Z5k</hvid>
  <hprice>$555</hprice>
  <hdesc>The Xbox One is a home video game console developed by Microsoft. Announced on May 21, 2013, it is the successor to the Xbox 360 and the third console in the Xbox family. It directly competes with Sony Computer Entertainment's PlayStation 4 and Nintendo's Wii U as part of the eighth generation of video game consoles. The Xbox One was released in North America, several European markets, Australia, and New Zealand on November 22, 2013, and in 26 other markets, including Japan, the remaining European markets, and the Middle East, in September 2014. It is also the first Xbox game console to be released in China, specifically in the Shanghai Free-Trade Zone. Microsoft and various publications have classified the device as an "all-in-one entertainment system", making it a competitor to other digital media players, such as the Apple TV and Google TV platforms.

Moving away from the Xbox 360's PowerPC-based architecture—back to the x86 architecture used in the original Xbox—the console features an Advanced Micro Devices processor built around the x86-64 instruction set. The Xbox One places an increased emphasis on cloud computing and entertainment integration, offering the ability to overlay live television programming from an existing set-top box with an enhanced program guide, split-screen multitasking of applications, and improved second-screen support. The console optionally includes an upgraded Kinect sensor, providing richer motion tracking and voice recognition for use in its graphical user interface (GUI) and games. The Xbox One also offers the ability for users to record and share highlights from or live-stream gameplay. The console's controller was refined over that of the Xbox 360, with a redesigned D-pad and triggers capable of delivering directional haptic feedback.

Prior to its official release, the Xbox One received mixed reviews: the entertainment-oriented features were praised, but there was controversy surrounding several policy changes since the Xbox 360's release, including a proposed always-on digital rights management (DRM) system, and privacy concerns over a mandate that the Kinect be used at all times. Microsoft retracted these changes prior to the console's launch, and it received mostly positive reception for its refined controller design, multimedia features, user interface, and voice navigation.</hdesc>
</hardware>

<hardware>
  <hname>Pre-built PC</hname>
  <himg>http://www.apsense.com/blog_photo/20130612/1371020734431914.jpg</himg>
  <hvid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ct_CvU-CsXI</hvid>
  <hprice>$400 - $2500</hprice>
  <hdesc>Customise the perfect match for your gaming needs! Start by selecting & mixing the best PC parts from our industry leading computer hardware partners!</hdesc>
</hardware>

<hardware>
  <hgame>Nintendo Wii U</hgame>
  <himg>http://www.runaroundtech.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/06/Nintendo-Wii-or-Wii-HD-II-is-Already-Close-and-More-Powerful-Than-Xbox-and-PS3.jpg</himg>
  <hvid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O2KB0TPROMI</hvid>
  <hprice>$350</hprice>
  <hdesc>The Wii U (Japanese: ウィー ユー Hepburn: Wī Yū?, pronounced /ˌwiː ˈjuː/) is a home video game console created by Nintendo and the successor to the Wii. The system was released in November 2012. As the first entry in the eighth generation of video game home consoles, it competes with Sony's PlayStation 4 and Microsoft's Xbox One.

The Wii U is the first Nintendo console to support high-definition graphics. The system's primary controller is the Wii U GamePad, which features an embedded touchscreen. The screen can be used either as a supplement to the main display (either providing an alternate, asymmetric gameplay experience, or a means of local multiplayer without resorting to a split screen), or in supported games, to play the game directly on the GamePad independently of the television. Games can support any combination of the GamePad, Wii Remote, Nunchuk, Balance Board, or Nintendo's more traditionally designed Classic Controller or Wii U Pro Controller for input. The Wii U is backwards compatible with most games released for the Wii. Online functionality on the Wii U centers around the Nintendo Network platform and Miiverse, an integrated social networking service which allows users to share content in game-specific communities.

The Wii U has faced mixed critical reception; while praising its GamePad controller (albeit panning it for its short battery life), improvements to its online functionality over the original Wii, its level of backwards compatibility with existing Wii software and controllers, its affordability in comparison to other eighth-generation consoles, and not requiring a subscription for online functionality, critics noted issues with certain aspects of the console's user interface and functionality, along with a weak lineup of launch titles and a lack of clear vision. The console was met with slow consumer adoption, credited primarily to an initially weak lineup of games, along with its lower specifications in comparison to the PlayStation 4 and Xbox One. In response to its poor adoption, several notable third-party studios, including Electronic Arts, announced that they would downplay their support for the console as part of their multi-platform strategies.

Adoption of the Wii U began to improve in 2013 following the release of several prominent first-party titles for the system, including The Legend of Zelda: Wind Waker HD, Mario Kart 8—which is currently the best-selling Wii U title worldwide, with over 5.43 million copies sold as of June 2015, and Super Smash Bros. for Wii U, which Nintendo claimed was the "fastest-selling" Wii U title, selling 490,000 copies in the United States in its first three days of availability</hdesc>
</hardware>

<hardware>
  <hgame>Nintendo 3DS XL</hgame>
  <himg>https://content.ebgames.com.au/website/images/detail/204713_detail.jpg</himg>
  <hvid>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PtQ0V734zxU</hvid>
  <hprice>$200</hprice>
  <hdesc>New Nintendo 3DS XL Console

More comfortable 3D gaming experience with the "Super-stable 3D function"

The super-stable 3D function is able to recognise the users face using the inner camera, automatically the angle even when you move a lot during gameplay. This way you can enjoy the best possible 3D experience.
Expanded control play with the new Control Stick and Buttons

With the new C Stick added on the top left corner of the A, B, X and Y Buttons, you can perform subtle moves by applying small movements.
ZR and ZL Buttons have been integrated in the console adding the function brought by the separate Circle Pad Pro into the console so that the extended play style is made possible by various software titles.
NFC function for amiibo compatible software

Not only can you play with your amiibo figure in real life, you can play with your amiibo figure in compatible software using the information stored inside the figure using NFC (Near-Field Communication) technology.
New Nintendo 3DS and New Nintendo 3DS XL have an area on the bottom screen with NFC reading and writing function built in, so you can enjoy playing with amiibo on compatible software.
Enjoy videos online

The Internet Browser installed on the console can play movie files. Surfing the internet is made easy by using the ZL/ZR Buttons to switch between the tabs as well as zooming into the page with the C Stick.
Please note: some movie files may not be compatible.
Customise your Home Menu with various Themes!

Designs will include Nintendo franchises such as Mario, Zelda and more.
You can customise your Home Menu by purchasing various Themes from the Theme Shop.
Some themes even have unique background music and sound effects.
Improved features and processing power

Nintendo are planning to release dedicated software for the New Nintendo 3DS and New Nintendo 3DS XL that utilises the improved performance of the new CPU. Some upcoming Nintendo 3DS software will enable improved graphics and gameplay performance on the New Nintendo 3DS system, and will also be compatible with the original Nintendo
Upgraded camera functionality

You can take better pictures under dim lighting conditions with the improved camera.
Using Wireless LAN, you can transfer data directly to and from your PC

If you have a PC that is connected to the Wireless LAN as the New Nintendo 3DS or New Nintendo 3DS XL, you can transfer your pictures and music without removing the mircoSD card.
Automatic Brightness Adjustment, Battery life Extended by improving energy consumption

The brightnesss of the screen is automatically adjusted to your surroundings. By automatically optimising the most appropiate brightness levle, the battery life extended when compared to the original Nintendo 3DS systems.</hdesc>
</hardware>
